<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bookstore Management System</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="desc1">


        <br>Author : J.K.Rowling\n</br>
        <br>Published Date : (1997-2007) \n</br>
<br>Paperback : $45.54\n</br>
        <br>It is vailable in 60 Languages\n</br>
    </string>

    <string name="desc2">

 <br>A Novel Of Africa\n</br>
        <br>Author : Elaine Neil Orr\n </br>
        <br>Published Date : April 2, 2013\n</br>
        <br>Total price: $26.79\n</br>
    </string>


    Ferdinand is a 2017 American computer-animated comedy adventure film produced by Blue Sky
    Studios and distributed by 20th Century Fox.

    <string name="desc3">


        <br>Author : Munro Leaf\n</br>
        <br>Published Date : 1936\n</br>
        <br>Produced By Blue Sky\n</br>
        <br>Studios and distributed by\n</br>
        <br>20th Century Fox.\n</br>
          <br>Paperback : 0.99$\n</br>
    </string>


    <string name="desc4">


        <br>Author : James Riley\n</br>
        <br>Published Date : December 15, 2015\n</br>
            <br>Paperback : $6.49\n</br>

    </string>


    <string name="desc5">

        <br>Author: Martin Waddell\n</br>
        <br>Published Date: 1992\n</br>
        <br>Page count: 32\n</br>
        <br>Original language: English\n</br>
        <br>Genres: Childrens literature\n</br>
        <br>Paperback : $7.49</br>
    </string>


    <string name="desc6">

       <br>Author: Chetan Bhagat\n</br>
        <br>Publisher: Rupa and Co.\n</br>

        <br>Genre: Fiction\n</br>
        <br>Pages: 280\n</br>

    </string>

    <string name="desc7">
        Are you looking for Bookstore management system for your final year project? We are here to help you. You can contact us This application based on Internet that aims to all the levels of management providing information of an organization. This system can be used as an information management system for the Bookstore. Final Year Project Help for Computer Science Where people can order the books which they want and even they do not need to bother about the location and do not worry about picking it up from the store. This system will help you to get the book from the store to your home just by a single click. We can also make the payment after delivery of the book which will make us feel safe regarding our money. The main menu will contain six parts which are as follows:
        Member Login
        Admin login
        About us
        Contact us
    </string>


    <string name="desc8">
        "Are you looking for Bookstore management system for your final year project? We are here to help you. You can contact us This application based on Internet that aims to all the levels of management providing information of an organization. This system can be used as an information management system for the Bookstore. Final Year Project Help for Web Developer, Android App Developer Where people can order the books which they want and even they do not need to bother about the location and do not worry about picking it up from the store.
This system will help you to get the book from the store to your home just by a single click. We can also make the payment after delivery of the book which will make us feel safe regarding our money. The main menu will contain six parts which are as follows:
Member Login,
Admin login,
About us Contact us!"
    </string>

    <string name="desc9">
        This process is so much time consuming and does not provide trust on retailers. There is the threat of forgery if you are new to marketing and do not know how to bargain from these streets sellers. There is no proper way of getting to know about the actual price of the books sometime shopkeepers sell it more than the market price by saying that the book is not available in the market. It might be the case that shopkeepers do not refund money if you purchase some wrong books. So, above this is the whole process of bookstore management system but by our system, we can make it little bit more simple and fast process to mechanize it. We can automate this process by creating the application which will allow you to use these things in a fully functional way and the application will include the following entities (an entity is a real-world object).
    </string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">hello_blank_fragment</string>



    <string name="desc10">
        All information regarding Book ISBN, edition status, and materials can change with the change of instructors, addition of sections and courses, or materials becoming outdated.We make every effort to ensure the accuracy of all the book and pricing information on this web site
    </string>

</resources>
